module two the modern entrepreneur's mindset avoiding analysis paralysis what that basically
entails you can't move because you are stuck thinking about stuff you are stuck thinking
about your service how do i perfect my service i'm not getting customers because my service
isn't perfect i'm not getting customers because my product isn't perfect not the case at all
it is because you are not taking actions towards reaching them i can't post because the content
isn't perfect my label for my product isn't perfect the powerpoint for my service for my sales speech
it's not perfect you just need to go you need to fail a hundred times before you might get that
first sale then you'll understand the entire journey i always see it as finishing the entire
video game you don't have to finish the entire video game just to get a sale right you just have to start
going start moving there are different levels to this right so you do want to take action
and this is a common theme that we see with different customers different clients of ours at terramore
too much information i need to take this course first i need to um build a perfect logo i need to
have my website perfect it just needs to exist for now right you have different problems if you don't
have 10 clients you have different problems if you don't have any clients you have different
problems if you have no traction on your instagram you have different problems if you have no traction
on your website everything should have some existence and then just go straight to the sale
you have to learn that first right i need the perfect script tool chasing i just need some other
software we hear all these things speed over certainty if you're 70 percent of the way there
action is the remaining 30 percent you'll realize that all of the things necessary in that sales call
you'll realize all of the things necessary when you're talking to a real customer that's why we kind
of want that repeatable process if it's not you know a repeatable process if it's some like one-off
conversation that only works for one specific type of customer you're going to have to do that
tens of dozens of depending on your service right hundreds of times you don't want that right at least not for
now continuing on this is just opportunity costs you're missing out on potential clients that your
customers are picking up learn that sales conversation and take action whether that's cold email cold dms
going through google and finding bad websites let's say you make websites going through google finding bad
websites let's say you build homes how am i going to find customers take action right whether that's
posting on your instagram whether that is hiring a videographer all of these things kind of need to
again take action
to do that set a cutoff date by
the end of march by the by friday by the end of the day i should be reaching out to five different people
right there are ways there are different tactics to get cold customers there are different tactics to get warm
customers there are different tactics to get the customers right in front of my face
and i need to explain what i do right now right there's that elevator pitch conversation
here's some examples of your cold dms just in case you want to copy and paste them right do that
figure it out take action so stop here continue on and do this this is really like it says copy paste
ready so you'll find starting the conversation might be your hardest hurdle
and if that's true copy paste this and start going
actions right just check these off if you haven't already pick your niche local dentists
um direct to consumer brands as we have as the examples here your single offer
right we don't want to over complicate this you should have multiple products within your
portfolio um but just for now repeatable process pick one and then choose your outreach channel am i
doing linkedin am i doing instagram am i doing snapchat am i doing google ads am i doing um phone calls
am i going door to door what am i doing and then commit to it for a week
action creates clarity you're going to understand exactly what you need to know don't have it all in
your head you're going to know exactly what you need to know here um i like the 70 rule you don't
need to get 100 of your service down 100 of your product down 100 of your outreach down 100 of your
website down um everything should be there exist but 70 of the way that remaining 30 you'll learn from
the customer and then like i said have deadlines if i don't do this then i will x right throw in that
if not this then that deadline cool all right see you in the next module